export const doctorQB = [
  {
    category: "Extraversion",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How much do you enjoy spending time with friends?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How comfortable are you in large groups of people (e.g., parties, events)?",
        choices: [
          "Very uncomfortable",
          "Uncomfortable",
          "Neutral",
          "Comfortable",
          "Very comfortable",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you usually start conversations with people you don't know well?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How often do you feel excited and full of energy?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How willing are you to try new activities or adventures?",
        choices: [
          "Not willing at all",
          "A little willing",
          "Somewhat willing",
          "Very willing",
          "Extremely willing",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Conscientiousness",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "How important is it for you to plan and organize your tasks or activities?",
        choices: [
          "Not important at all",
          "A little important",
          "Moderately important",
          "Very important",
          "Extremely important",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How often are you punctual for appointments or deadlines?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How much do you pay attention to small details in your work or tasks?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How dependable and responsible do you consider yourself to be?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When faced with a challenging task, how likely are you to keep working until it's completed?",
        choices: [
          "Not likely at all",
          "A little likely",
          "Somewhat likely",
          "Very likely",
          "Extremely likely",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Aptitude",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "If the price of a shirt is increased by 20%, by how much percent should its consumption be reduced so that the expenditure remains the same?",
        choices: ["16.67%", "14.32%", "16.50%", "12.84%"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "16.67%",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The ratio of boys to girls in a class is 3:5. If there are 36 girls, how many boys are there in the class?",
        choices: ["20", "15", "22", "27"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "22",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A shopkeeper sells an article at a profit of 20%. If the cost price is Rs.250, what is the selling price?",
        choices: ["500", "300", "50", "450"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "300",
      },
      {
        question:
          "A bag contains 4 red balls and 6 blue balls. Two balls are drawn at random. What is the probability that both balls are red?",
        choices: ["⅓", "⅘", "2/15", "6/21"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "2/15",
      },
      {
        question:
          "If 12 workers can build a wall in 9 days, how many days will it take for 8 workers to build the same wall?",
        choices: ["12 days", "10 days", "8 days", "13.5 days"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "13.5 days",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is the most likely conclusion to be drawn from the following statements? Statement 1: All cats are mammals; Statement 2: Some mammals are furry.",
        choices: [
          "All mammals are furry.",
          "Some cats are furry.",
          "Some furry animals are cats.",
          "All furry animals are mammals.",
          "None of the above.",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Some furry animals are cats.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is the most logical inference from the following statements? Statement 1: If it is raining, then the ground is wet; Statement 2: The ground is wet.",
        choices: [
          "It is raining.",
          "It is not raining.",
          "The ground is not wet.",
          "Both (a) and (b) are possible.",
          "None of the above.",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "It is raining.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is the most logical sequence of events? The sun rises; The birds start singing; People wake up; The flowers open.",
        choices: [
          "1, 2, 3, 4",
          "2, 1, 3, 4",
          "3, 1, 2, 4",
          "4, 1, 2, 3",
          "None of the above.",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "1, 2, 3, 4",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is the most accurate analogy to ‘A dog is to a puppy as a cat is to’:",
        choices: [
          "A kitten",
          "A mouse",
          "A lion",
          "A cheetah",
          "None of the above.",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A kitten",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is the most logical definition of the word mammal?",
        choices: [
          "A warm-blooded animal that gives birth to live young.",
          "A cold-blooded animal that lays eggs.",
          "An animal that has fur or hair.",
          "An animal that has four legs.",
          "None of the above.",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A warm-blooded animal that gives birth to live young.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Various terms of an alphabet series are given with one or more terms missing. Select the missing terms from the choices. AZ, GT, MN, ?, YB.",
        choices: ["KF", "RX", "SH", "TS"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "SH",
      },
      {
        question: "Poles: Magnet::? : Battery",
        choices: ["Energy", "Power", "Terminals", "Cells"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Terminals",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Kamal pointed to a photograph and says. 'The lady in the photograph is my nephew's maternal grandmother.' How is the lady in the picture related to the Kamla's sister if he has no sister of his own?",
        choices: ["Mother-in-law", "Cousin", "Sister-in-law", "Mother", "Aunt"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Mother",
      },
      {
        question:
          "An accurate clock shows 8 am. Through how may degrees will the hour hand rotate when the clock shows 2 pm?",
        choices: ["154°", "172", "130°", "160°", "180°"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "180°",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Domain Test",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "A _________ fuses with a _______ in generative fertilization",
        choices: [
          "Secondary nucleus, polar nucleus",
          "Polar nucleus, female gamete",
          "Male gamete, female gamete",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Male gamete, female gamete",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is a product of meiosis?",
        choices: [
          "Microspore mother cell",
          "Endosperm nucleus (primary)",
          "Megaspore mother cell",
          "Megaspore",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Megaspore",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following sexually transmitted diseases is caused by a virus?",
        choices: ["Syphilis", "Chlamydia", "Hepatitis B", "Cholera"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Hepatitis B",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the functions are performed by the ovaries?",
        choices: [
          "Formation of ovum",
          "Secretion of Progesterone",
          "Secretion of Estrogen",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "All of the above",
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following sterilization methods is permanent?",
        choices: ["Vasectomy", "Tubal Sterilization", "IUD", "(a) and (b)"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "(a) and (b)",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The process where characteristics are transmitted from parent to offsprings is called:",
        choices: ["Variation", "Heredity", "Gene", "Allele"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Heredity",
      },
      {
        question:
          "_______ is the observable set of characteristics of an organism",
        choices: ["Phenotype", "Genes", "DNA", "All of the above"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Phenotype",
      },
      {
        question: "Who proposed the theory of evolution?",
        choices: [
          "Charles Darwin",
          "Stanely Miller",
          "Harold Urey",
          "Aristotle",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Charles Darwin",
      },
      {
        question: "Which part of the DNA provides information for a protein?",
        choices: ["Chromosome", "Mitochondria", "RNA", "Gene"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Gene",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following can be inherited from parents to offspring?",
        choices: [
          "Swimming technique",
          "Big nose",
          "Sculpted body",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Big nose",
      },
      {
        question: "The _________ is the functional unit of environment.",
        choices: ["Genus", "Ecosystem", "Class", "Biome"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Ecosystem",
      },
      {
        question: "________ are producers",
        choices: ["Amoeba", "Mushrooms", "Sunlight", "Green plants"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Green plants",
      },
      {
        question: "_______ is a herbivore.",
        choices: ["Whales", "Eagle", "Bear", "Cow"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Cow",
      },
      {
        question: "A ____ is considered a terrestrial ecosystem",
        choices: ["Ocean", "Pond", "Underground caves", "Forest"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Forest",
      },
      {
        question: "_______ is an omnivore",
        choices: ["Panther", "Bear", "Wolf", "Lion"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Bear",
      },
      {
        question: "Ozone has the chemical formula ___________",
        choices: ["O5", "O4", "O3", "O2"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "O3",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When light rays enter the eye, most of the refraction occurs at the",
        choices: [
          "Crystalline lens",
          "The outer surface of the cornea",
          "Iris",
          "Pupil",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "The outer surface of the cornea",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In which part of the human eye is the image of an object formed?",
        choices: ["Iris", "Pupil", "Retina", "Cornea"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Retina",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The contraction and expansion movement of the walls of the food pipe is called:",
        choices: [
          "Translocation",
          "Transpiration",
          "Peristaltic movement",
          "Digestion",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Peristaltic movement",
      },
      {
        question: "The respiratory pigment in human beings is:",
        choices: ["Carotene", "Chlorophyll", "Haemoglobin", "Mitochondria"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Haemoglobin",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the percentage of oxygen in the expired air when a person is resting?",
        choices: ["12%", "16%", "20%", "24%"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "16%",
      },
    ],
  },
  

];

export const exampleQB = [
  {
    category: "Extraversion",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How much do you enjoy spending time with friends?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Conscientiousness",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "How important is it for you to plan and organize your tasks or activities?",
        choices: [
          "Not important at all",
          "A little important",
          "Moderately important",
          "Very important",
          "Extremely important",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Aptitude",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "If the price of a shirt is increased by 20%, by how much percent should its consumption be reduced so that the expenditure remains the same?",
        choices: ["16.67%", "14.32%", "16.50%", "12.84%"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "16.67%",
      },
      
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Domain Test",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "A _________ fuses with a _______ in generative fertilization",
        choices: [
          "Secondary nucleus, polar nucleus",
          "Polar nucleus, female gamete",
          "Male gamete, female gamete",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Male gamete, female gamete",
      },
     
    ],
  },
  

];

export const engineeringQB = [
  {
    category: "Extraversion",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How much do you enjoy spending time with friends?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How comfortable are you in large groups of people (e.g., parties, events)?",
        choices: [
          "Very uncomfortable",
          "Uncomfortable",
          "Neutral",
          "Comfortable",
          "Very comfortable",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you usually start conversations with people you don't know well?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How often do you feel excited and full of energy?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How willing are you to try new activities or adventures?",
        choices: [
          "Not willing at all",
          "A little willing",
          "Somewhat willing",
          "Very willing",
          "Extremely willing",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Conscientiousness",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "How important is it for you to plan and organize your tasks or activities?",
        choices: [
          "Not important at all",
          "A little important",
          "Moderately important",
          "Very important",
          "Extremely important",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How often are you punctual for appointments or deadlines?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How much do you pay attention to small details in your work or tasks?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How dependable and responsible do you consider yourself to be?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When faced with a challenging task, how likely are you to keep working until it's completed?",
        choices: [
          "Not likely at all",
          "A little likely",
          "Somewhat likely",
          "Very likely",
          "Extremely likely",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Aptitude",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "If the price of a shirt is increased by 20%, by how much percent should its consumption be reduced so that the expenditure remains the same?",
        choices: ["16.67%", "14.32%", "16.50%", "12.84%"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "16.67%"
      },
      {
        question: "The ratio of boys to girls in a class is 3:5. If there are 36 girls, how many boys are there in the class?",
        choices: ["20", "15", "22", "27"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "22"
      },
      {
        question: "A shopkeeper sells an article at a profit of 20%. If the cost price is Rs.250, what is the selling price?",
        choices: ["500", "300", "50", "450"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "300"
      },
      {
        question: "A bag contains 4 red balls and 6 blue balls. Two balls are drawn at random. What is the probability that both balls are red?",
        choices: ["⅓", "⅘", "2/15", "6/21"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "2/15"
      },
      {
        question: "If 12 workers can build a wall in 9 days, how many days will it take for 8 workers to build the same wall?",
        choices: ["12 days", "10 days", "8 days", "13.5 days"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "13.5 days"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most likely conclusion to be drawn from the following statements? Statement 1: All cats are mammals; Statement 2: Some mammals are furry.",
        choices: ["All mammals are furry.", "Some cats are furry.", "Some furry animals are cats.", "All furry animals are mammals.", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Some furry animals are cats."
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most logical inference from the following statements? Statement 1: If it is raining, then the ground is wet; Statement 2: The ground is wet.",
        choices: ["It is raining.", "It is not raining.", "The ground is not wet.", "Both (a) and (b) are possible.", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "It is raining."
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most logical sequence of events? The sun rises; The birds start singing; People wake up; The flowers open.",
        choices: ["1, 2, 3, 4", "2, 1, 3, 4", "3, 1, 2, 4", "4, 1, 2, 3", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "1, 2, 3, 4"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most accurate analogy to ‘A dog is to a puppy as a cat is to’:",
        choices: ["A kitten", "A mouse", "A lion", "A cheetah", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A kitten"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most logical definition of the word mammal?",
        choices: ["A warm-blooded animal that gives birth to live young.", "A cold-blooded animal that lays eggs.", "An animal that has fur or hair.", "An animal that has four legs.", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A warm-blooded animal that gives birth to live young."
      },
      {
        question: "Various terms of an alphabet series are given with one or more terms missing. Select the missing terms from the choices. AZ, GT, MN, ?, YB.",
        choices: ["KF", "RX", "SH", "TS"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "SH"
      },
      {
        question: "Poles: Magnet::? : Battery",
        choices: ["Energy", "Power", "Terminals", "Cells"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Terminals"
      },
      {
        question: "Kamal pointed to a photograph and says. 'The lady in the photograph is my nephew's maternal grandmother.' How is the lady in the picture related to the Kamla's sister if he has no sister of his own?",
        choices: ["Mother-in-law", "Cousin", "Sister-in-law", "Mother", "Aunt"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Mother"
      },
      {
        question: "An accurate clock shows 8 am. Through how may degrees will the hour hand rotate when the clock shows 2 pm?",
        choices: ["154°", "172", "130°", "160°", "180°"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "180°"
      },
  


    ]
  },
  {
    category: "Domain Test",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Which one of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",
        choices: [
            ".py",
            ".python",
            ".p",
            "None of these"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: ".py"
    },
    {
        question: "What do we use to define a block of code in Python language?",
        choices: [
            "Key",
            "Brackets",
            "Indentation",
            "None of these"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Indentation"
    },
    {
        question: "Which character is used in Python to make a single line comment?",
        choices: [
            "/",
            "//",
            "#",
            "!"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "#"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following operators is the correct option for power(ab)?",
        choices: [
            "a ^ b",
            "a**b",
            "a ^ ^ b",
            "a ^ * b"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "a**b"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the method inside the class in python language?",
        choices: [
            "Object",
            "Function",
            "Attribute",
            "Argument"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Function"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is the correct value of cot 100.cot 200.cot 600.cot 700.cot 800?",
        choices: [
            "1/√3",
            "√3",
            "-1",
            "1"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "1/√3"
    },
    {
        question: "If tan θ + cot θ = 2, then what is the value of tan100 θ + cot100 θ?",
        choices: [
            "1",
            "3",
            "2",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
        question: "If tan θ - cot θ = 0, what will be the value of sin θ + cos θ?",
        choices: [
            "1",
            "√2",
            "1/√2",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "√2"
    },
    {
        question: "The area of a rhombus is 240 cm2 and one of the diagonals is 16 cm. Find the other diagonal.",
        choices: [
            "16 cm",
            "20 cm",
            "30 cm",
            "36 cm"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "30 cm"
    },
    {
        question: "The height of a cylinder whose radius is 7 cm and the total surface area is 968 cm2 is:",
        choices: [
            "15 cm",
            "17 cm",
            "19 cm",
            "21 cm"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "15 cm"
    },
    {
        question: "The area of a trapezium is 480 cm2, the distance between two parallel sides is 15 cm and one of the parallel side is 20 cm. The other parallel side is:",
        choices: [
            "20 cm",
            "34 cm",
            "44 cm",
            "50 cm"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "44 cm"
    },
    {
        question: "A collection of hyperlinked documents on the internet forms the ?.?",
        choices: [
            "World Wide Web (WWW)",
            "E-mail system",
            "Mailing list",
            "Hypertext markup language"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "World Wide Web (WWW)"
    },
    {
        question: "The term HTTP stands for?",
        choices: [
            "Hyper terminal tracing program",
            "Hypertext tracing protocol",
            "Hypertext transfer protocol",
            "Hypertext transfer program"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Hypertext transfer protocol"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Microsoft window?",
        choices: [
            "Operating system",
            "Graphics program",
            "Word Processing",
            "Database program"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Operating system"
    },
    {
        question: "What is smallest unit of the information?",
        choices: [
            "A bit",
            "A byte",
            "A block",
            "A nibble"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A bit"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following memory cannot be directly accessed?",
        choices: [
            "Primary memory",
            "Secondary memory",
            "RAM",
            "DRAM"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Secondary memory"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these sets of logic gates are known as universal gates?",
        choices: [
            "XOR, NAND, OR",
            "OR, NOT, XOR",
            "NOR, NAND, XNOR",
            "NOR, NAND"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "NOR, NAND"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following physical quantity has S.I. unit J/C?",
        choices: [
            "Electric flux",
            "Dipole moment",
            "Electric Potential",
            "Electric field intensity"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Electric Potential"
    },
    {
        question: "The path of electrons in the presence of an electric field is:",
        choices: [
            "Straight",
            "Curved",
            "Zigzag",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Curved"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
        choices: [
            "LISP",
            "PROLOG",
            "Python",
            "Perl"
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Perl"
    },

    ]
  },

];



export const accQB = [
  {
    category: "Extraversion",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "How much do you enjoy spending time with friends?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How comfortable are you in large groups of people (e.g., parties, events)?",
        choices: [
          "Very uncomfortable",
          "Uncomfortable",
          "Neutral",
          "Comfortable",
          "Very comfortable",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Do you usually start conversations with people you don't know well?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How often do you feel excited and full of energy?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How willing are you to try new activities or adventures?",
        choices: [
          "Not willing at all",
          "A little willing",
          "Somewhat willing",
          "Very willing",
          "Extremely willing",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Conscientiousness",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "How important is it for you to plan and organize your tasks or activities?",
        choices: [
          "Not important at all",
          "A little important",
          "Moderately important",
          "Very important",
          "Extremely important",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question: "How often are you punctual for appointments or deadlines?",
        choices: ["Never", "Rarely", "Sometimes", "Often", "Always"],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How much do you pay attention to small details in your work or tasks?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "How dependable and responsible do you consider yourself to be?",
        choices: [
          "Not at all",
          "A little bit",
          "Moderately",
          "Quite a bit",
          "Very much",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
      {
        question:
          "When faced with a challenging task, how likely are you to keep working until it's completed?",
        choices: [
          "Not likely at all",
          "A little likely",
          "Somewhat likely",
          "Very likely",
          "Extremely likely",
        ],
        type: "MCQ",
        correctAnswer: " ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    category: "Aptitude",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "If the price of a shirt is increased by 20%, by how much percent should its consumption be reduced so that the expenditure remains the same?",
        choices: ["16.67%", "14.32%", "16.50%", "12.84%"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "16.67%"
      },
      {
        question: "The ratio of boys to girls in a class is 3:5. If there are 36 girls, how many boys are there in the class?",
        choices: ["20", "15", "22", "27"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "22"
      },
      {
        question: "A shopkeeper sells an article at a profit of 20%. If the cost price is Rs.250, what is the selling price?",
        choices: ["500", "300", "50", "450"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "300"
      },
      {
        question: "A bag contains 4 red balls and 6 blue balls. Two balls are drawn at random. What is the probability that both balls are red?",
        choices: ["⅓", "⅘", "2/15", "6/21"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "2/15"
      },
      {
        question: "If 12 workers can build a wall in 9 days, how many days will it take for 8 workers to build the same wall?",
        choices: ["12 days", "10 days", "8 days", "13.5 days"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "13.5 days"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most likely conclusion to be drawn from the following statements? Statement 1: All cats are mammals; Statement 2: Some mammals are furry.",
        choices: ["All mammals are furry.", "Some cats are furry.", "Some furry animals are cats.", "All furry animals are mammals.", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Some furry animals are cats."
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most logical inference from the following statements? Statement 1: If it is raining, then the ground is wet; Statement 2: The ground is wet.",
        choices: ["It is raining.", "It is not raining.", "The ground is not wet.", "Both (a) and (b) are possible.", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "It is raining."
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most logical sequence of events? The sun rises; The birds start singing; People wake up; The flowers open.",
        choices: ["1, 2, 3, 4", "2, 1, 3, 4", "3, 1, 2, 4", "4, 1, 2, 3", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "1, 2, 3, 4"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most accurate analogy to ‘A dog is to a puppy as a cat is to’:",
        choices: ["A kitten", "A mouse", "A lion", "A cheetah", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A kitten"
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the most logical definition of the word mammal?",
        choices: ["A warm-blooded animal that gives birth to live young.", "A cold-blooded animal that lays eggs.", "An animal that has fur or hair.", "An animal that has four legs.", "None of the above."],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "A warm-blooded animal that gives birth to live young."
      },
      {
        question: "Various terms of an alphabet series are given with one or more terms missing. Select the missing terms from the choices. AZ, GT, MN, ?, YB.",
        choices: ["KF", "RX", "SH", "TS"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "SH"
      },
      {
        question: "Poles: Magnet::? : Battery",
        choices: ["Energy", "Power", "Terminals", "Cells"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Terminals"
      },
      {
        question: "Kamal pointed to a photograph and says. 'The lady in the photograph is my nephew's maternal grandmother.' How is the lady in the picture related to the Kamla's sister if he has no sister of his own?",
        choices: ["Mother-in-law", "Cousin", "Sister-in-law", "Mother", "Aunt"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Mother"
      },
      {
        question: "An accurate clock shows 8 am. Through how may degrees will the hour hand rotate when the clock shows 2 pm?",
        choices: ["154°", "172", "130°", "160°", "180°"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "180°"
      },
  


    ]
  },
  {
    category: "Domain Test",
    questions: [
    
    {
    question: "Which of the following is not a core financial statement?",
    choices: [
    "The Income Statement",
    "Statement of Cash Flows",
    "The Trial Balance",
    "The Balance Sheet"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "The Trial Balance"
    },
    {
    question: "The income statement, which presents the results of operations, can be prepared in many forms including:",
    choices: [
    "Single Step Income Statement",
    "Condensed Income Statement",
    "Common Sized Income Statement",
    "All of the above"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following account types increase by debits in double-entry accounting?",
    choices: [
    "Assets, Expenses, Losses",
    "Assets, Revenue, Gains",
    "Expenses, Liabilities, Losses",
    "Gains, Expenses, Liabilities"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Assets, Expenses, Losses"
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following is true?",
    choices: [
    "Accounts receivable are found in the current asset section of a balance sheet.",
    "Accounts receivable increase by credits.",
    "Accounts receivable are generated when a customer makes payments.",
    "Accounts receivable become more valuable over time."
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Accounts receivable are found in the current asset section of a balance sheet."
    },
    {
    question: "A company that uses the cash basis of accounting will:",
    choices: [
    "Record revenue when it is collected.",
    "Record revenue when it is earned.",
    "Record revenue at the same time as accounts receivable.",
    "Record bad debt expense on the income statement."
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Record revenue when it is collected."
    },
    {
    question: "What are the main sections on a balance sheet?",
    choices: [
    "Assets, liabilities, income",
    "Assets, liabilities, equity",
    "Assets, liabilities, expenses",
    "Assets, gains, revenue"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Assets, liabilities, equity"
    },
    {
    question: "How are a company’s financial statements used?",
    choices: [
    "For internal analysis",
    "For external negotiation",
    "For compliance",
    "All of the above"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following scenarios increases accounts payable?",
    choices: [
    "A customer fails to pay an invoice.",
    "A supplier delivers raw materials on credit.",
    "Office supplies are purchased with cash.",
    "None of the above"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "A supplier delivers raw materials on credit."
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following must a certified public accountant (CPA) have in-depth knowledge of to pass the CPA licensing exam? (Check all that apply.)",
    choices: [
    "Accounting software packages",
    "Auditing",
    "Derivatives",
    "International banking laws"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Auditing"
    },
    {
    question: "What is the result of the following transaction for Company A? Company A’s customer is unable to pay for a previous credit sale in accordance with Company A’s 90-day payment terms. The customer makes a promissory note to Company A that extends payment over a 24-month term including 5% interest.",
    choices: [
    "No result because the customer didn’t pay.",
    "Accounts receivable increases because of the interest.",
    "A note receivable is recorded in non-current assets.",
    "Company A records the loan as a liability."
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "A note receivable is recorded in non-current assets."
    },
    {
    question: "When are liabilities recorded under the accrual basis of accounting?",
    choices: [
    "When incurred",
    "When paid",
    "At the end of the fiscal year",
    "When bank accounts are reconciled"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "When incurred"
    },
    {
    question: "Which is true about time in accounting?",
    choices: [
    "Current liabilities are debts payable within 2 years.",
    "Balance sheets reflect a company’s financial position at a certain point in time.",
    "The time value of money is a finance concept, not relevant in accounting.",
    "Accounts receivable are more easily collected as time passes."
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Balance sheets reflect a company’s financial position at a certain point in time."
    },
    {
    question: "When a company purchases property, plant, and equipment, how is it reflected on the statement of cash flows?",
    choices: [
    "As a source of cash in the cash from investing activities section",
    "As a source of cash in the cash from financing activities section.",
    "As a use of cash in the cash from investing activities section.",
    "As a use of cash in the cash from operating activities section."
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "As a use of cash in the cash from investing activities section."
    },
    {
    question: "What would the journal entry be for a company that takes out a five-year, $100,000 business loan?",
    choices: [
    "Debit $100,000 non-current asset, Credit $100,000 non-current liabilities",
    "Debit $100,000 current asset, Credit $100,000 non-current liabilities",
    "Debit $100,000 non-current liabilities, Credit $100,000 non-current assets",
    "Debit $100,000 current liabilities, Credit $100,000 current assets"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Debit $100,000 current asset, Credit $100,000 non-current liabilities"
    },
    {
    question: "Which accounts are associated with cost of goods sold?",
    choices: [
    "Accrued interest",
    "Depreciation",
    "Dividends",
    "Inventory"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Inventory"
    },
    {
    question: "Which organizations are involved in development of US Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (GAAP)? (Check all that apply.)",
    choices: [
    "Financial Accounting Standards Board (FASB)",
    "Government Accounting Standards Board (GASB)",
    "Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC)",
    "Federal Accounting Standards Advisory Board (FASAB)",
    "All of the above"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "All of the above"
    },
    {
    question: "Which inventory valuation method reflects the most current market value for inventory on hand?",
    choices: [
    "Last-in-First-Out (LIFO)",
    "Average Costs",
    "First-in-First-Out (FIFO)",
    "Specific Identification"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "First-in-First-Out (FIFO)"
    },
    {
    question: "Which of the following statements is not true about intercompany accounting?",
    choices: [
    "Intercompany transactions are between two units within the same legal entity.",
    "Intercompany transactions are eliminated in consolidated parent financial statements.",
    "They can significantly impact taxes.",
    "Intercompany transactions are between different legal entities under the same parent control."
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "They can significantly impact taxes."
    },
    {
    question: "Which is the method of depreciation used for US tax returns that is not GAAP-compliant?",
    choices: [
    "Straight-line method",
    "Modified accelerated cost recovery systems",
    "Double-declining balance method",
    "Units of production method"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Modified accelerated cost recovery systems"
    },
    {
    question: "What is the most-used method to amortize intangible assets on a company’s financial statements?",
    choices: [
    "Straight-line method",
    "Sum of the years digits method",
    "Double-declining balance method",
    "Units of production method"
    ],
    type: "MCQs",
    correctAnswer: "Straight-line method"
    }
    ]
    
    }
];